Mason Schleu

Software Engineer

5388 Lee St. #1211 Arvada, CO 80002 • (402) 658-6959 • mschleu231@gmail.com

SUMMARY

Agile Cyber Software Engineer with active Top Secret security clearance and 3+ years of programming experience deve loping Python and C++ test code. I currently work on a fast-paced, multidisciplinary team at Lockheed Martin where my job is to develop tests and detect bugs for the F-35 to ensure software meets customer requirements. My three main focuses are automation, testing, and cyber security.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Programming Languages: Python, C/C++/C#, Bash, Java, Assembly, Verilog, VHDL, HTML/CSS

Development: Unit testing, telemetry, debugging, optimization, data collection, technical reports, detail oriented

Programs: Jenkins, Jira, Bitbucket, Confluence, Microsoft Office, Visual Studio

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Cyber Software Engineer, Lockheed Martin - Cyber Network Interface Device (CNID)

December 2018 - present // Louisville, CO

- > Developed Python framework to automate the testing of thousands of CNID requirements.
- > Designed automated build and deploy system that streamlined team's development workflow.
- > Setup CI infrastructure, providing CNID sufficient time to test and ensuring on schedule delivery to customers.
- > Analyze nightly report data to detect and understand anomalies in the CNID using data to drive development and fixes.

Embedded Software Engineer, Lockheed Martin - Software Defined Satellites (SDS)

May 2018 - December 2018 // Louisville, CO

- > Developed the backend for the configuration service which handled requests from json, yaml, and ZooKeeper.
- > Wrote Sphinx and Doxygen documentation for all SDS services for developers and users.
- > Wrote unit tests using Google Test ensuring 100% code coverage.

Undergraduate Research Assistant, University of Nebraska, Omaha

Fall 2016 - Spring 2018 // Omaha, NE

- > Collaborated with medical doctors and human research subjects to develop user-friendly biomechanics devices.
- > Coded mobile smartphone apps in Java and C#to quantify sensor data from human motion.
- > Presented research at conferences to small audiences with wide range of backgrounds.

Software Developer Intern, National Strategic Research Institute

Spring 2017 - Spring 2018 // Omaha, NE

- > Developed AR applications for the Microsoft HoloLens in Unity using C#to enable gesture and voice control of planes.
- > Deployed and debugged AR applications in Visual Studio.
- > Communicated information to non-technical stakeholders via video tutorials and documentation.

PROJECTS

- > Team designed Android app, pcb, and embedded software to track foot temperature using Bluetooth sensors.
- > Self-taught web development in HTML/CSS and deployment using AWS to showcase my portfolio (link).
- > Android VR application using Unity, designed to challenge human subject's balance. Featured at Kaneko KINETIC art exhibit.

EDUCATION

B.S. Computer Engineering, University of Nebraska, Lincoln

2014 - 2018 // Omaha, NE - Peter Kiewit Institute

> President of the University of Nebraska Omaha Maker Group